Thor Wessel Lindberg

CONTACT

thorlindberg@icloud.com github.com/thorlindberg linkedin.com/in/thorlindberg apple.com/developer/thor-lindberg

ABOUT ME

I'm a 25-year old junior developer and digital designer, passionate about design systems, software architecture, and mobile applications.

I have 4+ years of educational experience with object-oriented programming, and 1+ year with event- and state-driven software development.

EDUCATION

MSc Information Technology (cand.it)

IT-University of Copenhagen, 2020-2022

BSc Health Information Science (bach.sund.it)
Copenhagen University, 2017-2020

LANGUAGES

Swift, JSX, JavaScript, TypeScript, Python, Java, Visual Basic for Applications, Lua, SQL, XML

TOOLS & FRAMEWORKS

Xcode, Visual Studio Code, Git, GitLab, MATLAB, CSS, SwiftUI, UIKit, Streamlit, React, Bootstrap, Figma, Excel, Tableau, Cytoscape

EXPERIENCE

Special Crime Unit (NSK)

IT-Administrative Student, 2021-2022 Financial Intelligence Unit

In this role I was responsible for the front-end development, documentation and maintenance of our web portal, in addition to developing and advancing applications and tools for internal data retrieval, manipulation and encoding.

Our team was split into pairs and tasks were assigned based on individual responsibilities.

IT-University of Copenhagen

Assistant Lecturer, 2022

UX Design II, Introduction to Programming

Teaching Assistant, 2021-2022

UX Design I, Introduction to Programming,

Experimental Design in Practice

In these roles I was responsible for planning and conducting exercise sessions as an extension of lectures, and answering student questions about the curriculum, terminologies and assignments.

Domino's Pizza

Store Leader, 2021-2022 Domino's Lyngby

In this role I was responsible for production and maintenance at our store, including inventory, payments, and delegating work to employees.